<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DrPatientAppointment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_register">RegisterActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_doctor">DoctorActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_patient">PatientActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_doctor_profile">DoctorProfileActivity</string>
    <string name="create_account">Create Account</string>
    <string name="login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="sign_up">SIGN UP</string>
    <string name="welcome">WELCOME</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm password</string>
    <string name="confirm">CONFIRM</string>
    <string name="tel">Tel</string>
    <string name="birthday">Birthday</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="google_signin_txt">Or Sign in with Google</string>
    <string name="signin_btn_clicked">Back to Login</string>
    <string name="create_account_unclicked">Create Account</string>
    <string name="my_patients">My Patients</string>
    <string name="patient_request">Patient Request</string>
    <string name="my_calendar">My Calendar</string>
    <string name="how_we_can_help_you_oday">How we can help you today?</string>
    <string name="appointment">Appointment</string>
    <string name="sign_out">SignOut</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="dr_address">Dr Johnny Sins General Medic, 11 Avenue Hell str, Kuzimu</string>
    <string name="dr_email">dr.sins@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="dr_tel">+212 (0) 5 37 64 95 15</string>
    <string name="dr_about">About</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="patient">Patient</string>
    <string name="dr_name">Doctor Johnny</string>
    <string name="my_calendar_txt">My Calendar</string>
    <string name="medical_folder">Medical Folder</string>
    <string name="choose_an_option">Choose an option</string>
    <string name="my_doctors">My Doctors</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="welcome_user">Welcome User</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="phone">Phone</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>

    <string-array name="form_type">
        <item>Consultation</item>
        <item>Hospitalisation</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="specialty_spinner">
        <item>Dentist</item>
        <item>General practitioner</item>
        <item>ORL</item>
        <item>Ophthalmology</item>
        <item>Pediatric</item>
        <item>Radiology</item>
        <item>Rheumatology</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="blood_spinner">
        <item>A+</item>
        <item>A-</item>
        <item>B+</item>
        <item>B-</item>
        <item>AB+</item>
        <item>AB-</item>
        <item>O+</item>
        <item>O-</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="textview">TextView</string>
    <string name="physical_information">physical Information</string>
    <string name="height">Height</string>
    <string name="weight">Weight</string>
    <string name="edit">edit</string>
    <string name="back">back</string>
    <string name="update_profile">UPDATE PROFILE</string>
    <string name="edit_my_profile">Edit My Profile</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>
    <string name="type">Type</string>
    <string name="treatment">Treatment</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="disease">Desease</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="message_your_doctor">Message your doctor</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="messages">Messages</string>
    <string name="add_doctor">Add Doctor</string>
    <string name="book">BOOK</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="appointment_purpose">Select your appointement purpose</string>
    <string name="thank_you">Thank you for choosing our service !</string>
    <string name="appointment_information">Appointment information</string>
    <string name="time">9:00 - 9:30</string>
    <string name="available">Available</string>
    <string name="all">All</string>
    <string name="general">General</string>
    <string name="dentist">Dentist</string>
    <string name="orl">ORL</string>
    <string name="ophthalmology">Ophthalmology</string>
    <string name="pediatric">Pediatric</string>
    <string name="radiology">Radiology</string>
    <string name="rheumatology">Rheumatology</string>
    <string name="hospitalisation">Hospitalisation</string>
    <string name="patient_name">Patient name</string>
    <string name="_12_06_2020_at_9pm">12/06/2020 at 9pm</string>
    <string name="status">Status:</string>
    <string name="about_me">about me</string>
    <string name="consultation">Consultation</string>
    <string name="_23_06_20_at_9pm">23/06/20 at 9pm</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="decline">Decline</string>
    <string name="_0652167895">0652167895</string>
    <string name="want_to_be_your_patient">Want to be your patient</string>
    <string name="view_form">View Form</string>
    <string name="doctor_name">Doctor NAME</string>
    <string name="appointement_type">Appointement type</string>
    <string name="_5_00_pm">5:00 PM</string>
    <string name="doctor">Doctor</string>
    <string name="timming">Timming</string>
    <string name="wed">WED</string>
    <string name="_19">19</string>
    <string name="july">July</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading</string>
    <string name="call_doc">Call your doctor</string>
    <string name="text_doc">Chat with your doctor</string>
    <string name="chat_doc">Chat with your doctor</string>
    <string name="call_pat">Call your patient</string>
    <string name="chat_pat">Chat with your patient</string>
    <string name="pat_img">Patient profile image</string>
    <string name="message_icon">message icon</string>
    <string name="send_message">Type your message</string>
    <string name="terms">By using this app, you agree to the</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">

        <![CDATA[
        <h1>Please read the terms carefully before using our app.</h1>

    <p>Welcome to Doctor appointment app. The content of the app pertains to Doctor appointment. The services of the app are essentially provided to bridge the information gap between patients and doctors.</p>

    <p>This document is an electronic record in terms of IT Act, 2000 and rules there under as applicable and the amended provisions pertaining to electronic records in various statutes as amended by the IT Act, 2000. This electronic record is generated by a computer system and does not require any physical or digital signatures. This document is published in accordance with the provisions of Rule 3 (1) of the IT (Intermediaries guidelines) rules, 2011 that require publishing the rules and regulations, privacy policy and terms of use for access or usage of the app.</p>

    <p>Your use of the app and services and tools are governed by the following terms and conditions ("Terms of Use") as applicable to the app including the applicable policies which are incorporated herein by way of reference. If you transact on the app, you shall be subject to the policies that are applicable to the Website for such transaction. By mere use of the Application, you shall be contracting with us and these terms and conditions including the policies constitute your binding obligations, with Doctor appointment.</p>

    <p>We request you to carefully go through these terms of use ("Terms of Use") before you decide to avail the services by registering with the company to avail our services, you irrevocably accept all the obligations stipulated in these terms of use and agree to abide by them. Accessing the app through any medium, including but not limited to mobile phones, smart phones and tablets, are also subjected to these terms of use. These terms of use supersede all previous oral and written terms and conditions (if any) communicated to you. By using this app, you signify your agreement to these Terms of Use.</p>

    <p>We reserve the right to modify or terminate any portion of the app or the services offered by the company for any reason, without notice and without liability to you or any third party. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review these terms of use periodically.</p>

    <p>We encourage you to independently verify any information you see on the app with respect to a doctor or healthcare provider that you seek to make an appointment registration: If you wish to schedule an appointment with a doctor or conduct a transaction on the app, you will have to register on the app and become a registered user prior to the completion of any transaction.To register, a user will have to provide information such as his/her name, email address and phone number and create a username and password.  Registration is only a one time process. We request you to please safeguard your password to your account on the app and make sure that others do not have access to it.</p>

    <p>It is your responsibility to keep your account information safe and current. A user may wish to schedule an appointment through his/her account for his/her family members and friends. While a user will be able to do this, please note that such user will be solely responsible for any activity that is undertaken through his/her account on behalf of his/her family members and friends.</p>

    <h2>INFORMATION UPLOADED BY YOU ON THE APP:</h2>

    <p>You understand that you may have the option of uploading your health / medical information on the Website in order to enable your doctor access your previous medical history. While we take utmost care with respect to the security of the information you decide to upload, you understand that any information that you disclose on the app is at your own risk. By uploading / sharing / disclosing your medical information on the App, you hereby give your consent to app to store such health / medical information on our servers. We will retain such medical / health information you upload on the app for as long as it is needed to fulfill the service you seek to avail on the app.</p>

    <p>If you delete your account, Contact Doctor will delete such medical / health information.</p>

    <p>But please note:</p>

    <li>There might be some latency in deleting this information from our servers and backup storage.</li>
    <li>We may retain this information if necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, or enforce our agreements.</li>

    <h2>SHARING OF INFORMATION UPLOADED BY YOU ON THE APP</h2>

    <p>Unless you specifically consent to share information, medical or otherwise, with either doctors or third-party service providers, app does not share such information that you upload on the app. While we take utmost care with respect to the security of the information you decide to share, you understand that any information that you disclose on the app is at your own risk. In the event you do not trust us with such information, please do not share such information on the app, while our endeavors to protect any information uploaded or shared by you on the app, you understand that we shall not be held liable or responsible for the loss or damage to such information on the app. It is your responsibility to ensure that you have all your information, medical or otherwise, stored on your hard drive. You hereby agree not to use the app as an "external storage" to store your medical / health records.</p>

     <h2>CLINICAL SUPPORT INFORMATION</h2>

    <p>We may provide information to assist you in clinical decision-making. This may include information and reminders concerning drug interactions, allergies, dosages, as well as general health-care related information and resources. The information and materials available through the app are for informational and educational purposes only and are not intended to constitute professional advice, diagnosis or treatment, or to substitute for your professional judgment.</p>

    <p>Information that may be placed on the app by third parties are beyond our control. We are not responsible for the accuracy or completeness of information available from or through our app. You assume full risk and responsibility for the use of information you obtain from or through this app, and you agree that we are not responsible or liable for any claim, loss, or liability arising from the use of the information. We do not recommend or endorse any provider of healthcare or health-related products, items or services, and the appearance of materials on the app relating to any such products, items or services is not an endorsement or recommendation of them. You agree to review the definitions, functionality, and limitations of the services and to make an independent determination of their suitability for your use.</p>

    <h2>SELECTING YOUR DOCTOR OR HEALTHCARE PROVIDER ON THE APP</h2>

    <p>The App allows you to select and schedule appointments with doctors and health care providers registered with the app and to whom certain specific terms apply. While choosing your doctor or healthcare provider on the App, you understand and accept that:</p>

    <p>You are ultimately responsible for choosing your own doctor or healthcare provider and we shall not be held responsible or liable for the selection of such doctor or healthcare provider.</p>
    <p>We will provide you with lists and/or profile previews of doctors and health care providers who may be suitable to deliver the health care that you are seeking based on information that you provide.</p>
    <p>For certain specific services, we may choose a doctor or healthcare provider on your behalf based on the nature of services you request and on the doctor or healthcare professional available to provide you with the clinical services for the same.</p>
    <p>Please note that we do not recommend or endorse any doctors or health care providers mentioned on the app.</p>
    <p>Does not make any representations or warranties with respect to these doctors or health care providers or the quality of the healthcare services they may provide.</p>

    <p>Information regarding doctors and health care providers and practice information found on the app is intended for general reference purposes only. Such information found on the app is mainly self-reported by the doctor or the health care provider. Such information often changes frequently and may become out of date or inaccurate. The app provides any advice or qualification certification about any particular doctor or healthcare provider. You are encouraged to independently verify any such information you see with respect to a doctor or healthcare provider that you seek to make an appointment with.</p>

     <h2>NO DOCTOR - PATIENT RELATIONSHIP</h2>

    <p>Please note that some of the content, text, data, graphics, images, information, suggestions, guidance, and other material (collectively, "Information") that may be available on the app (including information provided in direct response to your questions or postings) may be provided by individuals in the medical profession. The provision of such Information does not create a licensed medical professional/patient relationship between us and you and does not constitute an opinion, medical advice, or diagnosis or treatment of any particular condition, but is only provided to assist you with locating appropriate medical care from a qualified practitioner. We make no guarantees, representations or warranties, whether expressed or implied, with respect to professional qualifications, quality of work, expertise or other information provided.</p>
    <p>We do not in any way endorse any individual described herein. In no event shall we be liable to you or anyone else for any decision made or action taken by you in reliance on such information.</p>

    <h2>APPLICABLE LAW</h2>

    <p>The interpretation of this agreement and the resolution of any disputes arising under these terms of use shall be governed by the laws of Kenya.</p>

    <h2>REFUND AND CANCELLATION POLICY</h2>

    <p>In case of cancellation or non-confirmation of the appointment by Contact Doctor due to any reasons, three options are available to the consumer:</p>

    <p>He/She may ask for rescheduling the appointment with the specialist doctor.</p>
    <p>He/She may claim a refund of the advance payment.</p>
    <p>The advance payment may be added as credit in the account of the consumer and be adjusted in due course for future consultations.</p>
    <p>In case the consumer misses or cancels the appointment, he shall not be entitled to any refund.</p>

    <p>For claiming a refund, the consumer should necessarily have the valid invoice of the investigations, so as to be able to get the refund.</p>

    <h2>AVAILABILITY, APPOINTMENT, RESCHEDULING, FREE REVIEW AND OR CANCELLATION</h2>

    <p>E-consultations shall be available for family physician and multi-specialties E-consultation from a specific doctor/physician shall be available subject to his/her availability/willingness/discretion. Confirmation of your appointment with a specific doctor/physician, as per his/her availability, shall be sent to you via SMS and/or E-mail. We reserve the right to reschedule or cancel an appointment without any prior notice. The time provided for consultation to you is indicative and actual consultation time may change depending on the consulting doctors discretion. Your consulted physician reserves the right to provide post-consultation free review consultations can be booked, rescheduled or cancelled only within the stipulated time limits mentioned below:</p>

    <h2>PRIVACY AND SECURITY</h2>

    <p>We use secure encryption technology to keep your information safe and secured at all time. We are committed towards maintaining the privacy of the information uploaded by you on the app and complies with the industry standard security safeguards for the purpose of securing the app and the information provided/uploaded by you, we use all reasonable endeavors to ensure the integrity of the online payment facility\'s security. Despite our endeavors, breaches of security and confidentiality could occur. You acknowledge that we are not liable for any loss suffered by you as a result of any breaches in security modification of terms and conditions of service. We may at any time, without any prior notification to you, modify these terms and conditions. Please review the latest version of the terms and conditions before proceeding to avail the service. If you continue to use the service, it shall be deemed that you agree and abide by the modified terms and conditions.</p>

    <h2>PRIVACY ADDITIONAL TERMS</h2>

    <p>You confirm that you have read and accept our privacy policy. The privacy policy is hereby incorporated by reference into, and made a part of, these terms of use. Your use of the services is subject to any additional terms, rules, or guidelines applicable to the services or certain features of the services that we may post and you may accept (the "Additional Terms"), such as end-user license agreements for our downloadable applications, subject to Section 12 below. All such additional terms are hereby incorporated by reference into, and made a part of, the terms.</p>

    <h2>OWNERSHIP OF CONTENT</h2>

    <p>The services are owned and operated by........ The visual interfaces, graphics, design, compilation, information, computer code (including source code or object code), products, software, services, and all other elements of the services (the "Materials") are protected by copyright, trade dress, patent, and trademark laws, international conventions, and all other relevant intellectual property and proprietary rights, and applicable laws. All materials contained on the services are the property of or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies and/or third-party licensors. All trademarks, logos, and service marks displayed on the services, whether registered or unregistered, are owned exclusively by ....... or its affiliates and/or other third parties. Nothing contained in these terms of use, nor your use of the materials, shall be construed as granting you any license or right in or to any trademark, logo, or service. We reserve all rights not expressly granted in these terms of use.</p>

    <h2>BY USING THIS APP YOU REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT</h2>
<ul>
    <li>You are 18 years of age or older and that your use of the App shall not violate any applicable law or regulation.</li>
    <li>All registration information you submit is truthful and accurate and that you agree to maintain the accuracy of such information.</li>
    <li>Your registration on the app is solely for your personal and non-commercial use. Any use of this app or its content other than for personal purposes is prohibited.</li>
</ul>
<p>Your personal and non-commercial use of this app shall be subjected to the following restrictions:</p>
<ul>
    <li>You may not modify any content of the app.</li>
    <li>You may not decompile, reverse engineer, or disassemble the content;</li>
    <li>You may not remove any copyright, trademark registration, or other proprietary notices from the app.</li>
    <li>You further agree not to access or use this app in any manner that may be harmful to the operation of this app or its content.</li>
</ul>
    <p>You will not:</p>
<ul>
    <li>Use the service available on the app for commercial purposes of any kind or</li>
    <li>Use the app and or services in any way that is unlawful or harms the company or any other person or entity, as determined in the company\'s sole discretion.</li>
    <li>You will not post, submit, upload, distribute, or otherwise transmit or make available any software or other computer files that contain a virus or other harmful component.</li>
    <li>You will not impair or damage the app and / or services or any connected network, or otherwise interfere with any person or entity use or enjoyment of the Website and/or the Services.</li>
    <li>You will not engage in any form of antisocial, disrupting, or destructive acts, including "flaming", "spamming", "flooding", "trolling", "phishing", and "griefing" as those terms are commonly understood and used on the Internet.</li>
    <li>You will not delete or modify any content of the app and/or services, including but not limited to, legal notices, disclaimers or proprietary notices such as copyright or trademark symbols, logos, that you do not own or have express permission to modify.</li>

    <li>The company cannot and will not assure you that other users are or will be complying with the foregoing rules or any other provisions of these terms of use, and, as between you and the company, you hereby assume all risk of harm or injury resulting from any such lack of compliance.</li>

    <li>All information, content, and material contained in the app and/or services are the company\'s intellectual property. All trademarks, services marks, trade names, and trade dress are proprietary to the Company. No information, content, or material from the app and / or services may be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted or distributed in any way without the company\'s express written permission.</li>

    <li>You acknowledge that when you access a link that leaves the app, the site you will enter into is not controlled by the company and different terms of use and privacy policy may apply. By accessing links to other sites, you acknowledge that the company is not responsible for those sites.</li>
    </ul>
    ]]>

    </string>


</resources>